Guide to the Francis V. Keesling Papers, 1908-1972 (inclusive), 1947-1972 (bulk)
Department of Special Collections
Francis V. Keesling Papers,
1908-1972 (inclusive), 1947-1972 (bulk)
Special Collections M0258
Keesling, Francis V., 1908-
26 linear ft.
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None.
Provenance
Gift of Francis V. Keesling, Jr., 1973 and 1977.
Biographical Note
Francis Valentine Keesling, Jr., born 3 March 1908 in San Francisco, California, graduated from Yale University in 1930 and from Stanford University Law School in 1933. He practiced law in San Francisco from 1934 to 1955, and was with West Coast Life Insurance Co. 1936-1977.
Scope and Content
Correspondence, scrapbooks, legal papers, and miscellaneous material relating to the selective service, the construction of the San Francisco International Airport, and various government committees and projects.
Container List
- Air Academy (1949-50) (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Air Academy Data on legislation (1954) (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Air Pollution (1949-50) (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Air Terminal (1954) (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Airport (1948-51) (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Airport (1948-52) (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Airport (1950-53) (Box 1, Folder 7,8)
- Airport (1951-53) (Box 1, Folder 9,10)
- Airport (1951-54) (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Airport Admin. Bldg. Construction (1950-53) (Box 1, Folder 12,13,14)
- Airport - Alaskan route hearings (1950-51) (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Airport - Engineering data and costs (1950-51) (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Airport - Meeting with Secy. of Commerce (1952) (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Airport - Operators' Council - News & Comment (1954-55) (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Aviation (1950-53) (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Alcoholism meeting 3/27/68; Report to Legislature (1/5/67) (Box 2, Folder 20)
- State Department of Public Health (cnt'd.) [1C1-A] (1967-8) (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Traffic and Alcohol [1G1] (1967-8) (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Clippings [1H1] (1964-69) (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Stepping Stone Award to FVK jr. 4/4/66 [2H2] (1966-69) (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Resources [3K3] (1963) (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Treatment and Recovery Centers [1L1] (1964-69) (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Westside Community Mental Health Center [3L1] (1967-68) (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Tape on Alcohol [1M1] (1964) (Box 2, Folder 28)
- American Municipal Assn. (1953) (Box 2, Folder 29)
- American Municipal Assn. Conference (1949) (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Angel Island (1945-51) (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Anti-government Competition Board (1954) (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Appropriations (1954) (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Armed Services (1954) (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Art Association of SF (1951-56) (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Art Commission of SF exemption from fed. taxes (1953) (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Art Commission of SF (1951-54) (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Baker's Beach (1949-50) (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Ballet Guild (1953) (Box 2, Folder 39)
- BART [1C1] (1965-71) (Box 2, Folder 40)
- BART (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Bay Crossings (1947-50) (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Bay Crossings (1948-53) (Box 2, Folder 42,43)
- Bay Crossings (1949) (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Bay Crossings (1949-53) (Box 3, Folder 45-7)
- Bay Crossings (1953) (Box 3, Folder 48-51)
- Bay Crossings - Clippings (Box 3, Folder 52,54)
- Bay Crossings - Navy transcript (1953) (Box 3, Folder 55)
- Bay Crossings - Second (1947-9)FVK Sr. (Box 3, Folder 56)
- Bay Survey (1954) (Box 3, Folder 57)
- Birthplace of Fr. Junipero Serra (1952) (Box 3, Folder 58)
  (see also #191)
- Bomb Shelters (1950-1) (Box 3, Folder 59)
- Budget - Clippings (Box 3, Folder 60)
- Budget - Federal (1953) (Box 3, Folder 61)
- Camp Stoneman (1954) (Box 4, Folder 62)
- Candlestick Cove (1950-52) (Box 4, Folder 63)
- Census (1948-51) (Box 4, Folder 64)
- Chamber of Commerce, Bd. of Directors [1A1] (1966) (Box 4, Folder 65)
- Cherry River Project Dam #1 (1947-50) (Box 4, Folder 66-7)
- Cherry River Project (1948-9) (Box 4, Folder 68)
- Cherry River Project (1948-50) (Box 4, Folder 69)
- Cherry River Project (1949-50) (Box 4, Folder 70)
- Cherry River Project Dam #2 (1948-50) (Box 4, Folder 71,72)
- Cherry River Project (1950-51) (Box 4, Folder 73)
- Cherry River Project (1948-53) (Box 4, Folder 74)
- Cherry River Project (1949-53) (Box 4, Folder 75,76)
- Cherry River Project (1951-53) (Box 4, Folder 77)
- Cherry River Project (1952-53) (Box 4, Folder 78)
- Cherry River Project (1953-55) (Box 4, Folder 79)
- Cherry River Project Federal legislation (1949) (Box 4, Folder 80)
- Cherry River Project Finance (1953-4) (Box 4, Folder 81)
- Citizenship, 7th Natl. Conf. on (1952) (Box 5, Folder 82)
- Civil Center Development Master Plan (1953) (Box 5, Folder 83)
- Civil Defense (1948-50) (Box 5, Folder 84)
- Civil Defense (1951-4) (Box 5, Folder 85-8)
- Civil Defense (1950) (Box 5, Folder 89-92)
- Civil Functions SF (1952) (Box 5, Folder 93)
- Community Chest Bldg. Fund [3-456-BF] (1927-29) (Box 5, Folder 94)
- Community Chest Gen. File & Exec. Comm. [456] (1924-5) (Box 5, Folder 95)
- Congressional Salaries (1953-55) (Box 5, Folder 96)
- Construction of Additional Mil/Naval Academy (Box 5, Folder 97)
- Dam Construction (1954 (Box 5, Folder 98)
- Defense Production (1951-54) (Box 5, Folder 99)
- Diamond Heights - Clippings (Box 5, Folder 100)
- Downtown Planning Study CofC [3D1] (1967-68) (Box 5, Folder 101)
- Draft Deferments (1948) (Box 5, Folder 102)
- Eastern Airlines (1950) (Box 6, Folder 103)
- Eastern Airlines (1951-2) (Box 6, Folder 104,5)
- Eastern Airlines (1949-52) (Box 6, Folder 106)
- Eastern Airlines Application of, San Antonio-SF (Box 6, Folder 107-109)
- Eastern Airlines Briefs & Pleadings (1950-1) (Box 6, Folder 110-111)
- Economic Mobilization (Box 6, Folder 112)
- Education SF (1949-50) (Box 6, Folder 113)
- Education (1954) (Box 6, Folder 114)
- Electric Power Projects-Equipment (1954) (Box 6, Folder 115)
- Empire Hotel (1949) (Box 6, Folder 116)
- Excise Taxes (1954) (Box 6, Folder 117)
- Executive Reorganization Subcomm. CofC [2M1] (1968) (Box 6, Folder 118)
- Exemption of State and Mun. Securities fr. Fed. Tax (1951) (Box 6, Folder 119)
- Family Quarters - Personnel, DOD (1954) (Box 6, Folder 120)
- Federal Agency Shifts (1954-55) (Box 6, Folder 121)
- Federal Departments (1954) (Box 6, Folder 122)
- Fed. Legislation - Relief of City and Co. of SF (1949) (Box 6, Folder 123)
- Fed. Private Business Competition (1954) (Box 6, Folder 124)
- Fed. Property (1948)[re Funston?] (Box 6, Folder 125)
- Fed. Property (1954) (Box 6, Folder 126)
- Fed. Property Holdings (1944-53) (Box 6, Folder 127)
- Fed. Public Housing Program (1953) (Box 6, Folder 128)
- Federal Amusement Tax, Repeal of (1948-9) (Box 6, Folder 129)
- Fisherman (1954) (Box 6, Folder 130)
- Flagstad, Kirsten - clippings (Box 6, Folder 131)
- Flood Control (1953) (Box 6, Folder 132)
- Foreign Airlines (1954) (Box 6, Folder 133)
- Fort Funston (1948-50) (Box 7, Folder 134)
- Fort Funston Agreement (1949) (Box 7, Folder 135)
- Fort Funston Deeds (1949-53) (Box 7, Folder 136-8)
- Fort Funston Legislation (1949) (Box 7, Folder 139)
- Fort Miley (1949-50) (Box 7, Folder 140)
- Freeways CofC [5B1] Clippings (1965-8) (Box 7, Folder 141)
- Freeways (CHC) CofC [11B1] (1965) (Box 7, Folder 142)
- Freeways Notes [13B1] (1965) (Box 7, Folder 143)
- General Legislation (1952) (Box 7, Folder 144)
- Golden Gate Bridge (Box 7, Folder 145)
- Golden Gate Natl. Cemetery Rights of Way (1952-4) (Box 7, Folder 146)
- Golden Gate Natl. Cemetery Rights of Way (1953) (Box 7, Folder 147)
- Government Expenditures (1952-3) (Box 7, Folder 148)
- Government Reorganization, Expenditures & Promotion (1951) #1 (Box 7, Folder 149)
- Government Reorganization, Expenditures & Promotion (1951) #2 (Box 7, Folder 150-1)
- Government Reorganization, Expenditures & Promotion (1951) #3 (Box 7, Folder 152)
- Governmental Affairs Committee (Hull) CofC [1M1] (1969-71) (Box 7, Folder 153)
- Governmental Functions, Committee on (1953) (Box 7, Folder 154)
- Greek Refugees (1950) (Box 7, Folder 155)
- Hetch Hetchy (1952-55) (Box 7, Folder 156)
- Hetch Hetchy (1939-56) (Box 7, Folder 157)
- Hetch Hetchy Raker Act/Engle Bill (1954-55) (Box 7, Folder 158)
- Highways (1950-56) (Box 7, Folder 159)
- Housing (1947-56) (Box 7, Folder 160)
- Housing Washington DC (1956) (Box 7, Folder 161)
- Housing (1953-55) (Box 7, Folder 162,3)
- Housing (1947-53) (Box 7, Folder 164)
- Housing (1953) (Box 7, Folder 165,6)
- Hunter's Point Drydock (1949-50) (Box 7, Folder 167)
- Hunter's Point (1949) (Box 7, Folder 168)
- Insurance - Advanced Planning (1943-49) (Box 7, Folder 169)
- Insurance - ALC Annual Meeting (1972) (1971) (1970) (Box 7, Folder 170-72)
- Insurance - ALC Annual Meeting (1969, 68, 67) (Box 7, Folder 173-75)
- Insurance - ALC Future Meetings (& ALIC) (1972) (Box 7, Folder 176)
- Insurance - American Life Convention Assm [WCL 101] (1967-72) (Box 7, Folder 177,8)
- Insurance - American Life Insurance Assn. Merger (1972) (Box 7, Folder 179)
- Insurance - ACLIC [WCL 701] (1969-72) (Box 7, Folder 180)
- Insurance - Assn. General [WCL 1/2-01] (1967-71) (Box 7, Folder 181)
- Insurance - Cal. Ins. Fed'n., Inc. (1964-71) (Box 7, Folder 182)
- Insurance - Health Insurance Assn. of America [WCL 401] (1967-9) (Box 7, Folder 183)
- Insurance - Life Ins. Assn. of America -[WCL 601] (1966) (Box 7, Folder 184)
- Insurance - Tax'n. of Life Companies (1957-59) (Box 7, Folder 185,6)
- Insurance - West Coast Life (Box 8, Folder 187)
- Intergovernmental Relationships (1954) (Box 8, Folder 188)
- Internal Revenue (1955) (Box 8, Folder 189)
- Internal Revenue Clippings (Box 8, Folder 190)
- Internal Revenue Clippings (Box 8, Folder 191)
- Japanese Art Exhibit (1952-3) (Box 8, Folder 192)
- Junior Chamber International (1952-53) (Box 8, Folder 193)
- Junipero Serra (1952) (Box 9, Folder 194)
  (see also #54)
- Kern Co. Charter [1587] (1934-43) (Box 9, Folder 195,6)
- Kneass, George W. Company (1951) (Box 9, Folder 197)
- Knowland Campaign (2) (Box 9, Folder 198)
- Land (1954) (Box 9, Folder 199)
- Long-range Shipping Bill S241 (1952) (Box 9, Folder 200)
- Mails, rerouting of (1949) (Box 10, Folder 201)
- Mare Island (1949-50) (Box 10, Folder 202)
- Maringe Exchange (1954) (Box 10, Folder 203)
- Maritime (1951-54) (Box 10, Folder 204)
- Merchant Marine (1950-53) (Box 10, Folder 205-7)
- Mayors, US Conf. of (1950-52) (1952-54) (Box 10, Folder 208)
- Mayors, US Conf. of (1952) (Box 10, Folder 209)
- Mayors, US Conf. of (1953) (Box 10, Folder 210)
- Mint (1953) (Box 10, Folder 211)
- Mint (1955) (Box 10, Folder 212)
- Miscellaneous (1948-53) (Box 10, Folder 213-15)
- Montgomery, Ernest L. (10/25/50-8/13/53) (Box 10, Folder 216)
- Montgomery, Ernest L. (1954-55) (Box 10, Folder 217)
- Municipal Railway (1950-52) (Box 10, Folder 218)
- National Assn. of County Officials (1949-52) (Box 11, Folder 219)
- National Conf. of Lt. Governors (July 1967) (Box 11, Folder 220)
- National Forest Public Use Act (1967) (Box 11, Folder 221)
- National Production Authority - Broadway Tunnel (1951) (Box 11, Folder 222)
- National Production Authority -Itinerant (1952) (Box 11, Folder 223)
- National Production Authority -Lincoln High Gym (1951) (Box 11, Folder 224)
- National Production Authority -Public Works Projects (1951-2) (Box 11, Folder 225)
- National Production Authority -Recreation + Park Commission (Box 11, Folder 226)
- National Production Authority -School Construction (Box 11, Folder 227)
- National Production Authority -Sewage Treatment Plant (Box 11, Folder 228)
- National Production Authority - Sutro Reservoir/Connections (Box 11, Folder 229)
- National Production Authority - Swimming Pools (Box 11, Folder 230)
- National Production Authority - Water Dept. (Box 11, Folder 231)
- National Production Authority - Wire for Trolleys (Box 11, Folder 232-3)
- National Production Authority (Box 11, Folder 234-5)
- Palace of Fine Arts (Box 11, Folder 236-7)
- Pan-American Airways (Box 11, Folder 238-9)
- Pan-American Airways - Guatemala (Box 11, Folder 240)
- Panama Canal (Box 11, Folder 241)
- Panama Canal Tolls (Box 11, Folder 242)
- Parking Authority (Box 11, Folder 243)
- Parking Authority - St. Mary's Square Garage (Box 11, Folder 244-6)
- Payment in lieu of taxes (Box 12, Folder 247-52)
- Planning Commission (Box 12, Folder 253)
- Point Lobos Memorial (Box 12, Folder 254)
- Presidio (Box 12, Folder 255-58)
- Property Transfer (Box 12, Folder 259)
- Proposition 4, Repeal of (Box 12, Folder 260)
- Public Buildings (Box 12, Folder 261)
- Public Housing and Urban Redevelopment HR4663 (Box 12, Folder 262)
- Public Utilities - California (Box 12, Folder 263)
- Public Works, Committee on (Box 12, Folder 264)
- Reber Plan (Box 12, Folder 265)
- Reduction of Nonessential Federal Expenditures (Box 12, Folder 266)
- Release of Federal Housing (Box 12, Folder 267)
- Renfrow Luncheon (Box 12, Folder 268)
- Rent Control (Box 13, Folder 269)
- Reserve Fleet Rehabilitation (Box 13, Folder 270)
- Resolutions - Bd. of Supervisors (from 1954) (Box 13, Folder 271)
- Resolutions - Bd. of Supervisors (2/46-1953) (Box 13, Folder 272)
- Retirement Board (Box 13, Folder 273)
- SF Youth Assn. (Box 13, Folder 274)
- Santa Cruz Peninsula (Box 13, Folder 275)
- Schools (Box 13, Folder 276-7)
- Selective Service (Box 13, Folder 278)
- Selective Service - [499-15-A] (Box 13, Folder 279)
- Selective Service - Commdg. Officers Conference (1960) (Box 13, Folder 280)
- Selective Service - Conference (1957) (Box 13, Folder 281)
- Selective Service - (1957-9) (Box 13, Folder 282)
- Selective Service (Box 13, Folder 283)
- Selective Service - 1953Duty (Box 13, Folder 284)
- Selective Service - Natl. Military Training [620] (Box 13, Folder 285)
- Selective Service - 1949 (Box 13, Folder 286)
- Selective Service - 1952Conference (Box 13, Folder 287)
- Selective Service - 1961 (Box 13, Folder 288)
- Selective Service - Executive Reserve (Box 13, Folder 289)
- Selective Service - Standards for Induction (Box 13, Folder 290)
- Shipbuilding (Box 14, Folder 289)
- Shipbuilding clippings (Box 14, Folder 290)
- Slum Clearance -- Clippings (Box 14, Folder 288)
- Slum Clearance (Box 14, Folder 289)
- Small Boats Harbor Committee (Box 14, Folder 290)
- Smog (Box 14, Folder 291)
- Social Security -- Municipal Employees (Box 14, Folder 292-93)
- Social Security (Box 14, Folder 294)
- Social Security (1951-53) (Box 14, Folder 295)
- Southern Crossing (Box 14, Folder 296)
- Stamp Tax (Box 14, Folder 297)
- Steel Allocations (Box 15, Folder 298)
- Sunset Supply Line R/W Golden Gate Nat'l Cemetary (Box 15, Folder 299)
- Tanker Construction (Box 15, Folder 300)
- Taxation (Box 15, Folder 301)
- Taxation Municipal Bonds (Box 15, Folder 302)
- Tax on Grape and Wine Industry (Box 15, Folder 303)
- Taxes (Clippings) (Box 15, Folder 304)
- Temple Methodist Church (Box 15, Folder 305)
- Tidelands (Box 15, Folder 306)
- Traffic Safety Annual Meetings (Box 15, Folder 307)
- T.S. Board of Directors (Box 15, Folder 308)
- T.S. Correspondence (Box 15, Folder 309)
- T.S. Arthur D. Little Study (Box 15, Folder 310)
- T.S. Clippings (Box 15, Folder 311)
- T.S. Brochures (Box 15, Folder 312)
- T.S. Legislation (Box 15, Folder 313)
- T.S. AB2538 (Drunk Driving) (Box 15, Folder 314)
- T.S. Employment Contracts and Retirement Plan (Box 15, Folder 315)
- T.S. McAteer Act - current - SB466 (Box 15, Folder 316)
- T.S. - MAA - SB25 (Box 15, Folder 317)
- T.S. - MAA - SB25 (Box 15, Folder 318)
- T.S. - MAA - SB25 (Box 15, Folder 319)
- T.S. MAA - SB2538 Legislation -- Alcoholism (Box 15, Folder 320)
- T.S. - MAA - Hearings - Legislation -- Alcoholism (Box 15, Folder 321)
- T.S. - MAA - Correspondence (Box 15, Folder 322)
- T.S. - MAA - Rumford, Mavks Act - SB1279 (Box 16, Folder 323)
- T.S. Maintaining - MAA - SB338 (Box 16, Folder 324)
- T.S. - MAA - Governor's Task Force Committee 1970 (Box 16, Folder 325)
- T.S. - MAA - Governor's Task Force Committee 1970 (2) (Box 16, Folder 326)
- T.S. - MAA - G.T.F.C. - 1971 (Box 16, Folder 327)
- T.S. - MAA - G.T.F.C. - 1969 (Box 16, Folder 328)
- T.S. - MAA - G.T.F.C. - 1968 (Box 16, Folder 329)
- T.S. - MAA - G.T.F.C. - 1968 (Box 16, Folder 330)
- T.S. - MAA - G.T.F.C. - 1967 (Box 16, Folder 331)
- T.S. - MAA - G.T.F.C. - 1966 (Box 16, Folder 332)
- T.S. - MAA - G.T.F.C. - Nov. 1966 (Box 17, Folder 333)
- T.S. - MAA - FVK Jr.'s statement -- San Diego 9/6/60 -Hearing Assembly Interim Committee on Public Health (Alcoholism) (Box 17, Folder 334)
- T.S. - MAA - Federal Conferences and Reports -- Washington D.C. (Box 17, Folder 335)
- T.S. - MAA - Underwriter's Report - 1967Projections (Box 17, Folder 336)
- T.S. - MAA - Underwriter's Report 3/9/67 Ext. of MAA (Box 17, Folder 337)
- T.S. - MAA - Studies and Reports on Traffic Safety (Box 17, Folder 338)
- Troopship Committee (Box 17, Folder 339)
- Troopship (Clippings) (Box 17, Folder 340)
- United Nations (Box 17, Folder 341-2)
- Urban Development (Box 17, Folder 343)
- Vessels (Box 17, Folder 344)
- Veterans (Box 17, Folder 345)
- Veterans Hospital; correspondence re. Valejo (Box 17, Folder 346)
- Veterans Hospital Program (Box 17, Folder 347)
- Veterans (Korean) Educational Benefits (Box 17, Folder 348-49)
- Waldo Approach (Box 17, Folder 350)
- War Damage (Box 17, Folder 351)
- Washington Representation (Box 17, Folder 352)
- Y.M.C.A. (Box 17, Folder 353)
- VIII MISCELLANEOUS FILES
  - 1. Stanford University + Tutores, Considerations etc. JKC
    - A. Souveuir Autogreph Book of 14th Grand Chapter of Sigma Na Chicago 17/31/08 + 1/1-2/09 with fold-out cartoon Showing Keesling et al. (Vice Regent)
    - B. Pledge request for construction of Stanford Union Building
      - - Letter (TLC) [FVIC] to CareG. Brown 11/24/26re: 3 checks to Stanford Alumni Educational Fund $100 @ from FVK, Geo. Crother + Wm. H. Harretson
      - - Letter (TLS) Carl G. Brown to FVC 11/26/26 Thanks for above
      - - Letter (TLS) E.S. Erwin, Endowment Committee to FVK 6/3/26re check for $200
      - - Concerning Stanford VII#9 Res. Act. of the [UNK] 6/22
    - 1. C. (1) TLS J.P. Mitchell, Treasurer, Board of Athletic Control 1/27/1927re: $200 for Palmer Wilkinson Taylor Scholarship
    - Notice to Stanford Stadium subscribers 7/30 re tickets
    - Stanford Futures
    - TLS Herbert Hoover to Stanford Family re: above
    - TLc [PVK] to Fred A Geer 9/20/26re: Educ. Fund
    - TLc [PVK] to Paul M. Downing 9/20/26re: Educ. Fund
    - TLc [PVK] to W.H. Harrelson 9/20/26re: Educ. Fund
    - TLS Charles J. Crary [sp?] (Pres. Stanford Club SF) to FVK 5/15/30re checks & receipts attached
    - TLS Robert Anderson to FVK 1/1/29Branner Memorial [UNK] & clipping
      from Richard Barrett et al.
    - TL to Stanford & Stanford Alumnus 4/25/29re $
    - TLc (R/K) to JE McDonell 6/25/79possible donation of $6500 from Dr. Lawrence for a history of The University ?
    - TLc (FVK) to JW Howell (Stanford Club) 4/12/28
    - TLs JW Howell to (FVK) 4/11/28
    - TLc (FVK) to Carl G. Brown 4/6/28
    - TLc memo for Judge Crothers re Athletic Scholarship Fund 7/16/28
    - TLS Fred A. Geer to FVK 3/14/28 re: Athletic Scholarship Fund
    - TLc (FVK) to Carl G. Brown 4/6/28
    - TLc memo for Judge Crothers re: Athletic Scholarship Fund 2/16/1928
    - TLS Fred A. Geer to FVK 3/14/1928
    - TLc FVK to Wm. H. Harrelson 2/16/1928re: Athletic SCholarship Fund
    - TLc FVK to F.A. Geer 2/16/1928re: Athletic SCholarship Fund
    - TLc FVK to Paul M. Downing 2/16/1928re: Athletic SCholarship Fund
    - 1.C.(2) TLc FVK to Warren Hastings 1/16/26
    - ALS F.A. Geer to FVK 1/14/26
    - TLC FVK to Wm. Hastings 10/15/25
    - TLC FVK to Wm. Hastings 9/18/25
    - TLC memo re: $ 8/31/25
    - TLC FVK to Fred Geer 9/17/25
    - TLC FVK to F.L. Berry 10/18/22re: luncheon
    - TLC FVK to Arthur Joel 10/18/22re: luncheon
    - TLS Paul Sharp (Assoc. Oil) to FVK re: luncheon
    - TLS R.L. Wilbur (Chairman, Board of Trustees) 10/3/22to FVK re: Executive Com. Med. School meeting
    - TLS Ray Lyman Wilbur to FVK 9/28/22re: Endowment Committee
    - TLc FVK to D.P. Blodgett 9/21/22re: dinner Board of Trustees
    - TL invitation Board of Trustees to FVK 9/20/22
    - TLS J.E. McDowell (Alumni Secretary) to FVK 8/26/27
    - TLS John F. Sheehan, Jr. 8/17/27re: Athletic photos
    - TLC FVK to John F. Sheehan, Jr. 8/19/27
    - TLS Netwon [Cleveland ?] [to FVK] "Alumnus" 8/9/272 pp.
    - 2 notices of contributions to Stanford Alumni Association (1 blank) signed P.M. Downing and J.E. McDowell
    - 1 form letter, TS, Stanford Alumni Association to Stanford People 9/10/27and 1 carbon draft of same
    - 1.C.(3) TLc FVK to Paul M. Downing 8/23/27
    - ANS Paul M. Downing to FVK
    - TC form letter 8/11/27
    - TLS Stanford Alumni Association (P.M. Downing) to FVK et al. 7/30/27
    - TLc J.E. McDowell to Paul M. Downing 7/22/27
    - TL "copy" to Paul M. Downing re: fund solicitation policy
    - TLcS Paul M. Downing to FVK, 2 pp. 7/20/27
    - TL "copy" fragment of solicitation letter above
    - TLc "copy" fragment of solicitation letter above
    - ANS Don Seymour to FVK 11/29/26re: Stanford Club receipts
    - ALS Fred A. Geer to FVK 10/14/25
    - TLc FVK to Fred A. Geer 7/23/25
    - TLc FVK to Paul Downing 12/29/25
    - TLc FVK to Fred A. Geer 12/29/25
    - TLc FVK to F.E. Supple (Stanford University S.F. Club) 4/30/23
    - T Form L Stanford Club - H.H. Hall to "Stanford Men"
    - Draft TFL to High Schools "Stanford Education Funds" 1923
    - Draft TFL application form 1923
    - TLS copy Herbert Hoover to Wilbur 1/31/22re: Alumni solicitation
    - TLS 6/23/22Ray Lyman Wilbur to FVK re: Pres. of AMA election
    - Printed notice of Thanks signed Ray Lyman Wilbur for Endowment Fund
    - Pamphlet The First Million for Stanford
    - etc. - approx. 100 more
    - 2. Insurance (c. 1945)
    - 3. Repeal of Proposition 4 506-3 (pensions) 1949
    - 4. Cllipings & brochures - New Home Office Building SF [& BART]
    - 5. BART
    - 6. Golden Gate Bridge Highway & Transportation District
    - 7. Duplication copies of Introduction to Lt. Gen Lewis B. Hershey, Director of Selective Service System by FVK for SF 8/30/65
- Miscellaneous Files (2)
  - 1. Politics FVK - Knowland campaign 1952
  - 2. Politics U.S. Senate. W.F. Knowland S.F. Campaign material 499-9
  - 3. Economic Mobilization course 1950
  - 4. Torts - Professor Cathcart
  - 5. Contracts I - Professor Whittier
  - 6. FVK Mimeos 4/21/58re: Washington Representation to Board of Supervisors, San Francisco
  - 7. The Lamp Fall 1969(Golden Gate Bridge)
    Focus on: San Francisco-Oakland Metropolitan Area (B of A)
  - 8. Proposed Charter Amendments etc. 11/6/28
    used in drafting Charter for San Francisco, 1930.
  - 2-C. ALIC Books 18v. (American Life Insurance Co.)
  - 2-A. Congressional Record (4)
  - Congressional Directories (5)
  - Military Affairs Hearings (1)
  - 2-B Congressional Record (8)
  - Gen. Hershey's leg. officer 7/40 - 10/45
  - correspondence to Baruch / Clare Booth Luce, 5 files
  - Mayor Robinson's lobbyist: flood control, Bay Bridge, Knowland, etc. 1945, 6-7 files
DEPARTMENT OF SPECIAL COLLECTIONS: MANUSCRIPTS DIVISION
Books with Keesling Jr. ms. donation. (258)
Withdrawn from The Collection
- Padilla, Ambrosio., 3 vols.
  Criminal Law.
  Revised Penal Code.
  Manilla, Philippines.
  1944.
- Bureau of Public Painting.
  Public Laws.
  passed by The Philippine Commission.
  vol 1, 6, 19 & 22.
  Manila, 1903-1927.
- War Dept., USA.
  Annual Reports, 1907.
  vol 7--The Philippine Commission.
  (in 3 vols--we just have the first)
  Washington, Govt. Ptg. Office, 1908.
- Congressional Directory.
  - 89th Congress-2nd Session.
  - 90th Congress--1st and 2nd Sessions.
  - 91st Congress--1st and 2nd Sessions.
  - (5 vols.)
- Selective Service System.
  Reference Guide.
  Washington, D.C., 1953.
- Selective Service System.
  State Directors Conference.
  5-9 May 1969.
  Washington, D.C.
- U.S. Government Printing Office.